Guide to the Seattle Teachers' Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- SERIES III: MEETING AGENDAS AND MINUTES, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 5/31-6/33)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 6/32)
  - Minutes of other organizations, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 6/33)
- SERIES IV: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1954-1969 (Box-folder 6/34-6/40)
  - Budgets, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 6/34)
  - Budgets, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 6/35)
  - Financial reports, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 6/36)
  - Financial reports, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 6/37)
  - National Bank of Commerce, 1961 (Box-folder 6/38)
  - Payroll Deduction List, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 6/39)
  - IRS reports for Seattle Association of Classroom Teachers, 1954-1958 (Box-folder 6/40)
- SERIES V: REPORTS, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 7/1-7/22)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1961 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1962 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1963 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1964 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1967 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1968 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Washington Education Association, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - National Education Association, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - National Education Association, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - National Education Association, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - National Education Association Field Engagement Report, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Other teachers' organizations, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Seattle Alliance of Educators, 1968 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Seattle Public Schools, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Washingtion State Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Municipal League of Seattle and King County, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Disbursements from State construction fund, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Levy voting summary, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Interim Study of Education, 1960 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Miscellaneous reports, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 7/22)
- SERIES VI: PUBLIC INFORMATION RECORDS, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 7/23-7/39)
  - Speeches and writings (part 1 of 2), 1960-1965 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - Speeches and writings (part 1 of 2), 1960-1965 (Box-folder 7/24)
  - Seattle Teachers Association news releases, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 7/25)
  - Other organizations' news releases (part 1 of 3), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 7/26)
  - Other organizations' news releases (part 2 of 3), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 7/27)
  - Other organizations' news releases (part 3 of 3), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 7/28)
  - Press clippings, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 7/29)
  - Press clippings, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 7/30)
  - Press clippings, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 7/31)
  - Look Magazine article "What is a Teacher", 1956 (Box-folder 7/32)
  - Seattle Teachers Association newsletters, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 7/33)
  - Seattle Teachers Association newsletters, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 7/34)
  - Washington Education Association newsletters, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 7/35)
  - National Education Association newsletters, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 7/36)
  - Defense Bulletin, 1952-1958 (Box-folder 7/37)
  - Other organizations' newsletters, 1952-1964 (Box-folder 7/38)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box-folder 7/39)
- SERIES VII: ANNOUNCEMENTS, CIRCULARS, POLICY STATEMENTS, AND MEETING RECORDS, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 8/1-9/19)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1958 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1959 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Seattle Teachers Association, 1960 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 3 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 2), 1966- (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 3), 1967 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 3), 1967 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 3 of 3), 1967 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 1 of 5), 1968 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 2 of 5), 1968 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 3 of 5), 1968 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 4 of 5), 1968 (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Seattle Teachers Association (part 5 of 5), 1968 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Washington Education Association (part 1 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Washington Education Association (part 2 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 8/26)
  - Washington Education Association (part 3 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 8/27)
  - Washington Education Association (part 4 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 8/28)
  - Washington Education Association (part 5 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 8/29)
  - Washington Education Association: Teacher Position Listing Service, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Natonal Education Association (part 1 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Natonal Education Association (part 2 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Natonal Education Association (part 3 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Natonal Education Association (part 4 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Natonal Education Association (part 5 of 5), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Other teachers' organizations, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Seattle Alliance for Education, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Seattle Public Schools, 1950-1968 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Interim Committee on Education, Citizens Education Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Municipal League of Seattle and King County, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Seattle Chamber of Commerce, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Seattle Citizens Committee for School Support, 1963 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Seattle Citizens Committee for SRJ-1 and HJR-1, 1962 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Seattle Council of Parent-Teacher Associations, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Washington Council of Statewide Legislation, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Various organizations (part 1 of 2), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Various organizations (part 2 of 2), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 9/19)
- SERIES VIII: SUBJECT FILES, 1940-1968 (Box-folder 9/20-11/27)
  - American Association of School Administrators, 1967 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - American Education Week proclamation, 1959 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - American Federation of Teachers Seattle Local 200, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Committee chairmen, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Committee organization, 1960 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - Committee organization, 1961 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Committee organization, 1967 (Box-folder 9/28)
  - Contracts - teachers, 1965 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - Discipline, 1968 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Dues: what the $20 dues will provide, Undated (Box-folder 9/31)
  - DuShane Memorial Defense Fund, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Election of officers: ballots, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Employees: non-certificated, 1958 (Box-folder 9/34)
  - Evaluation check list, Undated (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Exchange teachers, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Faculty representative kickoff, 1968 (Box-folder 9/37)
  - Faculty representative dinner, 1969 (Box-folder 9/38)
  - General Certificates, 1940-1950 (Box-folder 9/39)
  - Health and Welfare Plan for Seattle School Employees, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 9/40)
  - Hood Canal Bridge, 1960 (Box-folder 9/41)
  - Ida Culver House, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 9/42)
  - Insurance: annuities, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 9/43)
  - Insurance: dreaded disease coverage, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 9/44)
  - Insurance: Educators Insurance Co., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 9/45)
  - Insurance: group disability and medical, 1951-1966 (Box-folder 9/46)
  - Insurance: retiree coverage, Undated (Box-folder 9/47)
  - Insurance: Seattle Public Schools group policies, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 9/48)
  - Insurance: STA auto liability, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 9/49)
  - Insurance: WEA-sponsored group plans, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 9/50)
  - Junior High curriculum, 1950 (Box-folder 9/51)
  - Legislative appropriation request, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 9/52)
  - Legislative candidate interviews, 1966 (Box-folder 9/53)
  - Legislative collection, 1959 (Box-folder 9/54)
  - Legislative dinner, 1958 (Box-folder 9/55)
  - Legislative dinner, 1959 (Box-folder 9/56)
  - Legislative dinner, 1960 (Box-folder 9/57)
  - Legislative dinner, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 9/58)
  - Legislative dinner, 1966 (Box-folder 9/59)
  - Legislative dinner, 1968 (Box-folder 9/60)
  - Legislative lists, 1958 (Box-folder 9/61)
  - Legislative maps, c. 1958 (Box-folder 9/62)
  - Legislators' questionnaire, 1960 (Box-folder 9/63)
  - Legislators school visit day, 1960 (Box-folder 9/64)
  - Legislature: Interim Committee on Education, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Federal aid to education, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Federal legislation, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Federal legislation, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - 37th Legislature, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Legislation: Washington State (part 1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Legislation: Washington State (part 2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - 39th Legislature, 1965 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Magazine: Seattle Teachers advertising, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Magazine: Seattle Teachers advertising, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Membership, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Membership (part 1 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Membership (part 2 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Merger proposal: Seattle Grade Teachers Club and Seattle Association of Classroom Teachers, 1956 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Newsletter material, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Nothing so certain: filmstrip script and requests, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Objectives, 1959 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Office equipment, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Overseas teacher relief, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Overseas teaching positions, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Petitions, c. 1960 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Public housing, 1950 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Public relations, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Public relations, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Retirements, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Retirements, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Retirements, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Retirement System, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Prefessional salaries: the key to quality education, WEA report, 1958 (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Salaries and taxes, 1960 (Box-folder 10/30)
  - STA Salary study, 1962 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Salary proposals (part 1 of 3), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 10/32)
  - Salary proposals (part 2 of 3), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Salary proposals (part 3 of 3), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 10/34)
  - Teachers' salary compared with nurses', 1957 (Box-folder 10/35)
  - Scholarships, 1961 (Box-folder 10/36)
  - Hilda Maehling Fellowship Fund, 1960 (Box-folder 10/37)
  - School District property use re Luther Burbank and Martha Washington sites, 1967 (Box-folder 10/38)
  - School tax levy contributions, 1959 (Box-folder 10/39)
  - Seattle Citizens School Levy Committee, 1960 (Box-folder 10/40)
  - School tax levy, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/41)
  - School Board dinner, 1961 (Box-folder 10/42)
  - Tax deductions, 1967 (Box-folder 10/43)
  - Teachers organizations of other cities (part 1 of 3), 1958-1960 (Box-folder 10/44)
  - Teachers organizations of other cities (part 2 of 3), 1958-1960 (Box-folder 10/45)
  - Teachers organizations of other cities (part 3 of 3), 1958-1960 (Box-folder 10/46)
  - Teacher performance appraisal, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 10/47)
  - Tenure law, Undated (Box-folder 10/48)
  - Thom McAn award, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 10/49)
  - Tours, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/50)
  - UNESCO, 1950 (Box-folder 10/51)
  - Vancouver elementary school teachers visit, 1960 (Box-folder 10/52)
  - California Teachers Association, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - King County Assessor, c. 1959 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - King County Coordinating Council, 1948-1959 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - King County Coordinating Council, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - King County Coordinating Legislative Council, 1950, Undated (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Municipal League of Seattle and King County, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Northwest Regional Educational Laboratory, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Seattle Association of School Secretaries, 1960 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Seattle Chamber of Commerce, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Seattle Council of Parent-Teacher Associations, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - Seattle Historical Society, 1953-1960 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Seattle Public Schools. Facts and figures about your Seattle Public Schools, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Seattle Public Schools finance and operating, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Seattle Public Schools finance, budget, levies (part 1 of 2), 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Seattle Public Schools finance, budget, levies (part 2 of 2), 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - Seattle Public Schools Superintendent's office (part 1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Seattle Public Schools Superintendent's office (part 2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Seattle Public Schools Superintendent's Bulletin, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Seattle Public Schools Superintendent's Bulletin, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Seattle Public Schools teachers, 1960 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Seattle Public Schools permits for use of school building, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - State Board of Education, c. 1960 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Spokane Education Association, 1959 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Student Washington Education Association. Handbook for student leaders, 1966 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Washington Council on State Legislation, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Washington State School Directors' Association, 1964 (Box-folder 11/27)
- SERIES IX: COMMITTEE RECORDS, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 11/28-13/8)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/28)
  - Building Committee, 1960 (Box-folder 11/29)
  - Building Representatives Conference, 1959 (Box-folder 11/30)
  - Building Representatives Conference, 1960 (Box-folder 11/31)
  - Building Representatives notices, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/32)
  - Seattle Citizens School Progress Planning Committee, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11/33)
  - Continuous Progress Center Concept Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 11/34)
  - Constitution Committee, 1963 (Box-folder 11/35)
  - Special Task Force on Discipline, 1968 (Box-folder 11/36)
  - Elementary School Representatives, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11/37)
  - Elementary School Representatives, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 11/38)
  - Ethics Committee, Undated (Box-folder 11/39)
  - Executive Secretary Committee, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 11/40)
  - Five Days Committee, 1961 (Box-folder 11/41)
  - Future Teachers of America Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Future Teachers of America Committee, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Improvement of Instruction Committee, 1961 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Improvement of Instruction Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Insurance Committee, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Insurance Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Insurance Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - International Relations Committee, 1963 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Legislative Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Legislative Committee, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Legislative Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Legislative Committee, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Legislative Dinner Committee, 1964 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Legislative Dinner Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Magazine Evaluation Committee, 1960- (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Membership Committee, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Membership Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Membership Committee, 1963 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Membership Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - New Teacher Orientation Committee, 1958 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - New Teacher Orientation Committee, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Nominating Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Nominating Committee, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Nominating Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - 180 Day Committee, 1956 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - PTA Presentations Committee, Undated (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Policies and Objectives Commission, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Primary Problems Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Professional Negotiations Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Professional Rights and Responsibilities Commission, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - Professional Rights and Responsibilities Commission (part 1 of 2), 1964-1967 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Professional Rights and Responsibilities Commission (part 2 of 2), 1964-1967 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/34)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12/35)
  - Retirement Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/36)
  - Retirement Committee, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/37)
  - Retirement Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/38)
  - Retirement Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/39)
  - Salary Committee (part 1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/40)
  - Salary Committee (part 2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/41)
  - Salary Committee, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/42)
  - Salary Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/43)
  - Social Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/44)
  - Social Committee International Fiesta, 1959 (Box-folder 12/45)
  - Social Committee, 1960 (Box-folder 12/46)
  - Social Committee, 1961 (Box-folder 12/47)
  - Social Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/48)
  - Special Levy Campaign Contributions Committee, 1958 (Box-folder 12/49)
  - Standing Committees, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/50)
  - Standing Committees, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/51)
  - Tax-sheltered Annuities Subcommittee, 1963 (Box-folder 12/52)
  - Teacher Education and Professional Standards (TEPS) Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 12/53)
  - Teacher Education and Professional Standards (TEPS) Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 12/54)
  - Teacher Education and Professional Standards (TEPS) Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12/55)
  - Teacher Load Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Teacher Load Committee working conditions survey, 1958 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Teacher Load Committee, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Teacher Load Committee - Elementary, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Teacher Load Committee - Secondary, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Teacher Load Committee floating teacher proposal, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Telephone Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - UNESCO Committee, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 13/8)
- SERIES X: RECORDS OF ACTIVITIES WITH AFFILIATED ORGANIZATIONS, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 13/9-14/56)
  - Subseries A: National Council of Urban Education Associations, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 13/9-13/15)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations Miami meeting, 1966 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations San Diego meeting, 1966 (Box-folder 13/11)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations Dallas meeting, 1967 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations meetings, 1967 (Box-folder 13/13)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations St. Paul meeting, 1968 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - National Council of Urban Education Associations convention, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Subseries B: National Education Association, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 13/16-13/33)
  - NEA Development Project, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - NEA legislative, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 13/17)
  - NEA legislative bulletins, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 13/18)
  - NEA Legislative Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Local consultants to NEA committees, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 13/20)
  - NEA Research Division, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Timely Tips, 1959 (Box-folder 13/22)
  - NEA Legislative Conference, 1958 (Box-folder 13/23)
  - NEA Convention, St. Louis, 1959 (Box-folder 13/24)
  - NEA Convention, 1960 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - NEA Convention, 1961 (Box-folder 13/26)
  - NEA Convention, 1965 (Box-folder 13/27)
  - NEA Convention (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 13/28)
  - NEA Convention (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 13/29)
  - NEA Convention (part 1 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 13/30)
  - NEA Convention (part 2 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 13/31)
  - NEA Convention (part 3 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 13/32)
  - Association of Classroom Teachers of the NEA Northwest Regional Conference, 1968 (Box-folder 13/33)
  - Subseries C: Washington Education Association, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 13/34-14/56)
  - Meeting minutes, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 13/34)
  - Meeting minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 13/35)
  - Meeting minutes (part 1 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 13/36)
  - Meeting minutes (part 2 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 13/37)
  - Meeting minutes (part 1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 13/38)
  - Meeting minutes (part 2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 13/39)
  - Meeting minutes (part 1 of 2), 1963 (Box-folder 13/40)
  - Meeting minutes (part 2 of 2), 1963 (Box-folder 13/41)
  - Meeting minutes (part 1 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 13/42)
  - Meeting minutes (part 2 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 13/43)
  - Meeting minutes, 1965 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1966 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Meeting minutes, 1967 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Meeting minutes, 1968 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - WEA Representative Assembly minutes, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - WEA Representative Assembly minutes, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - WEA Representative Assembly, 1959 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - WEA Representative Assembly, 1960 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - WEA Roundup leadership conference, 1958 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - WEA Roundup leadership conference, 1959 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - WEA VIP Conference, 1959 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - WEA regional convention planning, 1959 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - WEA Legislation Committee, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - WEA unit presidents and legislative chairmen, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - WEA Salaries, School Finance and Taxation Committee, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - WEA Operation School Evaluation Progam, 1958 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers workshop, 1958 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers Bellingham meeting, 1959 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers Ellensburg meeting, 1960 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers meetings, 1961- (Box-folder 14/20)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers Yakima meeting, 1963 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers Olympia meeting, 1964 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers Seattle meeting, 1964 (Box-folder 14/23)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers Vancouver meeting, 1966 (Box-folder 14/24)